<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fictions on Kurtis Rainbolt-Greene&#39;s Web Log</title>
    <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fictions on Kurtis Rainbolt-Greene&#39;s Web Log</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2005-2018 Kurtis Rainbolt-Greene</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An old tale</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/an-old-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/an-old-tale/</guid>
      <description>He walked for as long as the light of day shined in the skies. I watched the mad vagrant cross from street to alley way and back. His tattered cloak protected him from the bright sun, but not the jeers of children. His worn boots protected his feet from the sharp rocks, but not the hooves of horses or the mail boots of the militia. I followed the staggering fool from the library entrance all the way to the slums of the eastern city and I knew not why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossus: Cold Steel</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/colossus-cold-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/colossus-cold-steel/</guid>
      <description>The Metal Colossus
Not like the brazen giant of Earth fame,
With conquering limbs astride from star to star;
Here at our meteor-washed, Jupiter Gates shall stand
A mighty warrior with a fusion cell, whose laser
Is the imprisoned lightning, and his name
Father of Lions. From his beacon-hand
Glows system-wide welcome; his fierce eyes command
The warp-bridged station that twin moons frame.
&amp;ldquo;Keep, ancient nations, your storied pomp!&amp;rdquo; cries he</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark King</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/dark-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/dark-king/</guid>
      <description>His voice got all craggy like, and he thrust his pipe with the vigorous emphasis, &amp;ldquo;Muah father was told by his father. His father was told by his father. My great-great-great grand-mother spun this tale to him, &amp;lsquo;cus his father was struck down by a carp!&amp;rdquo; The children all shuddered at the thought, &amp;ldquo;But the story goes like this, with some minor changes and additions&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; The room went dark, his eyes glowed, there were no words from anyone but the red bearded bard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero&#39;s Call</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/heros-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/heros-call/</guid>
      <description>Call For Heroes A game based in a original fantasy setting. Players will be either Heroes or Villains in the Two Forest Village, a budding area of both mirth and dread. The Empire Gerbani is drowning in its own misery and weariness. The soldiers fight on two fronts, at the deserts to the south where the prospect of gold and riches drew the lecherous eyes of kings and nobles looking to finance the war to the west.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iplo: A Written Language</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/iplo-a-written-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/iplo-a-written-language/</guid>
      <description>On a lark I decided to design my own alphabet. I had no prior experience, but it I figured it would be fun to theorycraft. I had these goals:
 Simple for the machines Learn tricks from machine languages Parsable even with small print Contexts like sarcasm  Here&amp;rsquo;s the template for each character:
 ◌ ◌ ◌ □ □ □ □ □ □ □ □ □ ◌ □ ◌  Here&amp;rsquo;s an example character:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Grand Importance</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/of-grand-importance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/of-grand-importance/</guid>
      <description>The bard plucked at his lute with a zen like focus, &amp;ldquo;We continue the tale from where we left off. Can any of you tell me what happened last?&amp;rdquo; Many of the children squealed and raised their tiny hands. &amp;ldquo;Oh! The Prince died!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;No that hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened yet, stupid!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I know! The smelly Zed left Ruby for that other place.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Python!&amp;rdquo; Holding up his worn hands the bard signaled for the children to calm down, &amp;ldquo;Correct!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top World</title>
      <link>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/top-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kurtis.rainbolt-greene.online/fiction/top-world/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The top world was grey. A dead grey like the skin of my father. The various top world blankets rolled across the horizon and back. An invisible sea above the teams head. None of us were prepared for this sort of adventure, many had never had so much as a peek of the outside. Most puked, some cried, and others like myself simply stood silent. We were seven outcasts, charged by the King to find fortune in another mountain as punishment for our wrong doings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>